zenithoptimedia.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy – Zenith

### Who is the controller of your personal data?

The pages on this website (“the website”) are managed and operated by ZenithOptimedia Limited (referred to hereafter as “we” or “us”).

This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information that you provide to us or which we collect about you when using this website.   We’ve updated our privacy policy in line with the requirements set out by General Data Protection Regulation.

Your privacy is a serious matter to us and we have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of how we collect, use, share, and secure your Personal Information. “ **Personal Information** ” includes your full name, address, e-mail address, other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you, and any other non-personally identifiable information associated with Personal Information. This Privacy Policy explains, in general, what Personal Information and other information is collected on the Website, how the information is used, and with whom we may share such information. Please take a few minutes to read our Privacy Policy so that you understand how Zenith treats your Personal Information. It is our general policy not to share your Personal Information with third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes without your consent.

What information do we collect about you?  

Zenith may collect information in a number of ways in connection with the Website, including, without limitation, as follows:

  * When you submit a resume or other information to be considered for employment with Zenith.
  * When you send us an enquiry via the contact form on our website
  * When you subscribe to one of our Global Intelligence publications and reports
  * When you request to receive our newsletters
  * When you voluntarily provide Personal Information to us for any other purpose.

We collect information about you when you register with us or request information from us about our products and services. The type of information that we collect from you will include: your name, your company, your email address, your phone number.

We will also collect information about your use of this website. Website usage information is obtained via the use of cookies (please see ‘cookies’ section below).

### How will we use your information?

The information collected will be used to send you the information you have requested from us and will, where agreed to by you, be used to provide you with information about our products and services. All personal information collected about you shall be processed in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.  When sending us an enquiry a backup of your data will be held for 30 days but only authorised individuals will be able to access your data during this period.

We may pass on your personal information to our group companies within the ZenithOptimedia network so that they may provide you with information on their products and services that may be of interest to you. However we will never share your personal information for marketing purposes with companies outside of the ZenithOptimedia group network.

### Marketing

We would like to send you information about our (and our group companies’) products and services which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing information from us (or a group company), you may opt out from such marketing communications at any time.

If you no longer wish to be contacted by us, please email info@zenithmedia.com.

### Access to your information and correction

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of the personal information that we hold about you, please email us at info@zenithmedia.com.

We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. Therefore you can also contact us at any time to ask us to correct or remove information that you think is inaccurate.

### Cookies

Our website uses cookies. The cookies we use are ‘analytical’ cookies. They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors to our website and enable us to analyse how visitors move around the website when they are using it. This helps us to improve your experience of this website, for example by making sure you can find the information you are looking for easily.

For further information on cookies, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org.

You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above website shall tell you how to remove them from your browser. However in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.

### Other websites

Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.

### Changes to our privacy policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this webpage.

### How to contact us

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:

By email: info@zenithmedia.com

Effective Date: 21 May 2018.
